♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
This program is brought
to you by Fruit Bouquets.
Got a birthday coming up for
someone you absolutely hate?
Why not tell them to go screw themselves
by sending a giant Fruit Bouquet?
With just a few clicks, you'll be able
to send someone 14 pounds of
unwanted decorative produce
that will go bad within
an hour of arrival!
Hungry for a strangely-warm strawberry?
How about a hard green wedge
or a slime-glazed melon ball?
Well, we have all these gross things.
Order now and make someone feel guilty
about throwing it straight into
the trash six hours later.
Fruit Bouquets: the rotting
gift with flies on it!
Okay, I'm heading out for ladies' night.
There's a casserole in the refrigerator.
I'll be home at 11:00.
- Hey, Lois?
- Yeah?
How would you find out the
name of the actual actress
who plays the AT&T chick?
I left a list of hot commercial girls
on the refrigerator.
What is this "refrigerator"
you keep mentioning?
Are you talking about
the sandwich house?
I guess I'm not the only person
with a useless husband.
I mean, look at Mrs. Butterworth.
I still don't understand why
we couldn't take my last name.
Well, my last name helps
keep a roof over our head
and pays for your hobby.
Hobby?
Oh, look at that.
My business line is ringing.
Hello? Lamps That Look
Like Soccer Balls.
Yes?
Okay. How many would you like to return?
Yeah, just send them here, care of...
Mr. Butterworth.
Ah, it's so nice getting
out of the house.
If I had to change one more
diaper, I was gonna lose it.
I'm in exactly the same boat.
I mean, what would our husbands do
if they had to change their own diapers?
Different boat, Bonnie.
Much different boat.
Hey, I got an idea.
Let's crank call them.
Me first.
You're weak, Cleveland!
You're worthless and weak!
You found Brown.
Hello, Cleveland.
This is Michelle Obama.
It is?!
Yes. I received all your letters,
and I do like your mustache.
Oh. I've been doing all
your arm exercises.
Thank you, but those won't
work on your fat arms.
How do you know my arms are fat?
I deliberately left them
out of all the photos.
You're eating a pie on the
toilet, aren't you, Cleveland?
Who is this? Is this a Jerky Boy?!
It's your wife, you big dummy!
I used to have my own show.
Hello?
Hello. Is this Joe Swanson?
Wait. You can talk normal?
What do you mean?
Never mind.
We're calling from WQHG,
Quahog's Hottest Hits.
And we'll give you $500 if
you can sing Britney Spears'
"I'm Not A Girl, Not Yet A Woman."
You've got ten seconds to...
♪ I'm not a girl, not yet a woman ♪
♪ All I need is time... ♪
Oh, but you have to be able to walk.
Aw, nuts.
Okay, my turn! My turn!
Hello. Don't say anything
about the 1998 Oscars.
I'm watching it now.
Hello, is this Peter Griffin?
If this is the fracking
people, I have made it clear
that I am 100% on board.
No, my name is Rebecca.
You've never met me before
and probably don't even know I
exist, but you're my father.
Hello?
How'd you get this number? Don't
you ever call here again!
What the hell?!
He just got mad and hung up.
He what? Why?
I don't know. He sounded weird.
Like when he was an NFL
announcer and had to pretend
he cared about the shows after the game.
Patriots calling their
third and final timeout.
Hey, after the game, keep it here
for an all-new Madam Secretary.
Tonight, Madam Secretary faces
an international crisis in Pakistan,
while her teenage daughter
faces her own crisis
finding a date for the prom.
Madam Secretary, tonight on CBS.
Is this the longest
time-out of all time?
Hey, Peter.
So, um, anything interesting
happen tonight?
Yup. I finally peed that chunk
of poo off the side of the bowl.
You know the one you've
been yelling at me about?
Nobody... called or anything?
Nope. So, hey, uh, are you tipsy enough
to let me have lazy Tony Soprano sex?
You know, where-where I just lie there
and arch my hips a little bit
and breathe like a dying whale?
Uh, I don't know.
All right, well, just in
case, I'll be upstairs
getting into my boxers and black socks.
Do you think it's possible
he actually has an illegitimate child?
I don't know, but something's going on,
because I'm telling you,
he lied right to my face.
Sometimes friends put
wine out for each other.
I just don't understand it.
I mean, we don't keep
secrets in this house.
We didn't even keep the
Pop Secret's secret.
Psst. Hey, did you hear?
Hear what?
Orville Redenbacher is gay.
But he has a son.
He's in the commercial.
His son's gay, too. They're both gay.
They have sex parties
in the Hollywood Hills.
It sounds like you're
just making up stories
about your competitors.
You're gay, too.
What?
Aah! You're a psycho!
Dad, you're never gonna believe what...
Chris, meet Orville Redenbacher
and his son. Watch.
And that's where we get the expression
"gay as a bag of popcorn."
All right, I'll see you later.
What? Where are you going?
Laser tag orientation.
Well, that's obviously not true.
Yeah, that boy got lie-arrhea.
Oh, my God. I-I got to follow him,
find out where he's really going.
Good idea. If I was you,
I'd stick to him like glue-arrhea.
Okay, I think I'm starting
to crack your code.
Quick, Brian, I need your car.
I don't know, Lois.
You're not on the insurance,
and I don't think that...
Fruit Bouquet for Brian Griffin?
Happy birthday, buddy.
What the hell?
Peter, what are you doing here?
Lois! Uh, uh...
I was... I'm just, uh, shopping.
Yeah, I'll-I'll take a
large sperm, please.
Nice going, now you've ruined Christmas.
Peter Griffin, you tell me
what's going on right now.
Okay, fine, I'll be honest with you.
A long while back, just
before we got married,
I was a little short of cash.
What, to buy our rings?
No, I wanted to pay for dial-up
modem impression classes. See?
Wow, that's pretty good. I...
You've got mail.
Okay, but hang on. You
were a sperm donor?
Yeah, I'd-I'd almost forgotten about it,
but then last night, I get
this call from a woman
who says she's my daughter.
Peter, that was me. I
was prank calling you.
You what?!
I can't believe you would do that to me!
Can you guys argue elsewhere?
You're making it tough
to finish in here.
No, fight louder! Call her a bitch!
But I don't understand.
Why did you come here today?
'Cause that call last
night gave me a scare.
I figured if I do have a kid out there,
I want to make sure they're not
giving out my information.
They're not supposed
to; I signed a form.
Hold on, Peter.
I'm sorry I tricked you,
but if you do have a child out there,
isn't it only fair to let
him or her meet you?
Eh, maybe you're right.
I mean, as long as we're here,
maybe you should sign a consent form.
Okay, yeah.
All right, I'll do it.
You know what?
It feels good doing
something nice for others.
Like when I was a mentor for Kid Rock.
Okay, I took a leak into
this can of Busch Light
without spilling.
You're ready.
You don't need me anymore.
Will I see you again, Peter?
Wherever a father weighs
less than his daughter,
I'll be there.
Wherever someone has a
banner for a football team
as a curtain, I'll be there.
Wherever there's a fight
in a Waffle House,
I'll be there.
Now go.
People need a concert to go
to after the water park.
Hi, is, uh, is Peter Griffin here?
Oh, my God.
Is everything okay?
Yes, it's just... you look just like...
What's going on? Who's this supermodel?
I'm Katie.
I'm your daughter.
You're what?
Holy crap!
Yeah, I hope you don't mind the drop-in,
but the, uh, the sperm bank said
it was okay to contact you.
Wow, I guess, I guess I just
didn't expect this so soon.
Well, we were all pretty
excited to meet you.
What do you mean "we"?
Hi, Dad!
We're all your children.
We came from your semen.
"Semen."
- "Semen."
Ha-ha!
Oh, sorry. Wrong house.
Look, Eddie's at the wrong house.
- Ha-ha!
Peter, how many times
were you a sperm donor?
Only once, but I had just seen
Uma Thurman in Beautiful Girls,
so it was kind of a ka-blamo.
You ever seen those videos where
they put Mentos in Diet Coke?
Uh, listen, I want all of you to know
how happy we are to meet you.
In fact, this calls for a celebration.
Can you all stay for dinner?
Aw, we'd love that. Wouldn't we, guys?
Yeah, absolutely.
You said it, babe.
Yeah, Chinese Peter very hungry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down there, Lois.
Just 'cause they're my kids
and they all look like me
doesn't mean we have anything in common.
Daddy.
I've never felt proud of any
of my children until now.
This is so exciting.
For years, I have dreamed of
one day traveling from Bavaria
to play the accordion
for my birth family.
May I?
I have just one question for you.
What are those?!
Oh, I get that because this comedy
has just made it to Germany.
Wow, you look exactly like me.
Yes, I'm not actually part
of sperm donation thing.
I'm your secret clone.
We have been Orphan Black-ed
and you soon will be dead.
Meg, where are you?
I'm right here, Mom.
Well, look at your fine ass.
Are you talking to me?
Damn right.
I've been looking
around this whole house
for something to nibble on.
I think I just found it.
So many confusing feelings!
- Dad.
- Sex.
Black woman.
Historically-low mortgage rates.
Ah! I got to go buy a house.
Lois, Lois.
Can I keep the little person Peter?
No. They're too much work.
But I'll take care of it. I promise.
You always say that, and
I'm the one who ends up
feeding him and walking him
and doing all the clean up.
Excuse me, I'm a candidate
for a doctorate in Classics at Wesleyan.
It talks! Lois, it talks!
Whoa, that was close.
You almost dipped one of
your yabbos in the marinara.
Let me help you with those.
Well, thank you. That's so sweet.
You're the first person who
looks anything like my husband
who's offered to help in any way.
Oh, you must be Peter's wife, Lois.
I'm Larry.
It's nice to meet you, Larry.
Weird hands-full pinky shake?
I got to tell you, it's so strange,
you look so much like Peter
when I first met him.
Well, I'm guessing you look
exactly the same, too.
You're in such great shape.
Well, I do have tiny blue
weights in my garage.
Oh, hi, Larry.
Hi, Lois. Is Peter here?
Larry, it's only 2:00 in the afternoon.
Peter's still sleeping
off last night's party.
Then why... why are you still
in your pajamas and bathrobe?
Oh, that's because I'm depressed.
Is that why that sad
Shel Silverstein blob
is following you around?
Who would ever me?
Anyway, we didn't really get a chance
to finish our conversation yesterday,
and I thought maybe we could
grab some lunch together.
Huh. That would give me a
reason to get dressed today.
Oh. Would you, uh, like to join us?
That didn't sound like
a real invitation.
See, this is why no one
ever wants to you.
Thank you again for lunch, Larry.
Sorry I drew so many Nazi
symbols on the place mat.
- I was just nervous.
- That's okay.
I just wish we hadn't gone
to a kosher restaurant.
Ugh, but look at me.
I got ice cream all over my fingers.
Do you have a napkin?
No, but let me help you clean it off.
Larry, are you turned on or starving?
Can't it be both?
- Mm.
Wow, Larry, that was unexpected.
Shh, we'll discuss this later.
- I have to get back to my high school...
- Oh.
- Where I work...
- As a janitor...
- Oh.
- To pay for medical school...
- That I'm building...
- Oh!
- Out of Popsicle sticks.
- Oh.
That big one doesn't
blink a lot, does he?
Hey, Lois, where's your purse?
Me and some of my kids
are going to the movies.
By the way, Dwarf Peter died.
I didn't know what he ate,
so I gave him nothing.
His name was Tyler.
He had a name.
Everything you say, you say with pride.
I like that about you.
Anyway, where's Larry?
Maybe he wants to go to the movie.
Larry?
Why would I know where Larry is?
And who is Larry?
Well, never mind.
All right, everybody bring your phones
so we can text each
other during the movie.
Wow, you want to tell me what that was?
Oh, Brian, Larry and I sort
of crossed a line yesterday.
I don't know, he's just
so sweet and fun-loving,
and for God's sake,
he looks just like Peter
did when he was his age.
Yeah, but...?
Well, he kissed me and
I kind of let him.
I told him it could never
happen again and that...
What are you doing?
Oh, I-I thought that was kind of
like, "I'm open for business."
No! I'm confiding in a friend.
Oh! You're the safe friend.
Look, I feel awful about it,
but I told Larry that was it,
and we couldn't be anything
more than friends.
So, you're still gonna see him?
Yes, of course; he's a nice young man
and he's practically family.
Lois!
No! Zoloft Blob, don't!
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I-I'm fine, I just
hurt my neck this morning
vigorously nodding
approval to Judge Judy.
Okay, all right, the doctor is in.
Come on, back it up over here.
Somebody's got a neck massage coming.
Ah, right there.
Okay, but let's keep this friendly.
You can choke me for just a second.
You know, maybe I should just go
ahead and do your whole back.
Yeah, your bra strap is
getting in the way here.
I'll just bite it off with my teeth.
Lois, is a president
stronger than a king?
What the hell?!
Oh, Peter.
L-Look, calm down. We're just friends.
H-He's just giving me
a friendly massage.
A friendly massage?!
Yeah, and what do you care?
When's the last time you
did anything nice for me?
I ate that gross pasta you made.
I might as well just tell you, Peter.
I'm in love with Lois.
I knew it the moment we kissed.
Kissed?!
Is that true?!
Yes, Peter, but I...
You son of a bitch!
Everybody says, "We don't need
a homeowners' association.
That's stupid, Quagmire."
Well, this is why a
homeowners' association.
What the hell?!
Lois?!
What'd you do that for?
I thought you and him were
girlfriend and boyfriend.
He was not my boyfriend, Peter.
And I wasn't about to stand by
and watch him kick your ass.
I was holding my own there.
You were getting beat up.
No, no, I meant I was
holding my own nuts
so he wouldn't kick them.
But if he's not your
boyfriend, why'd you kiss him?
He kissed me.
And I should've told you.
I'm sorry if I hurt you, Peter.
I guess Larry just reminded me
of a younger version of you,
and the truth is,
I liked that he was paying
me a little attention,
the way you used to.
Maybe I have been
taking you for granted,
but I promise I'll make it up to you.
I'll be the best husband ever.
You already are.
For God's sakes, when
push came to shove,
you stood toe-to-toe with a much
younger man and fought for me.
Oh, hey, by the way, uh,
thanks, all my kids,
for stepping in to help.
Really, really appreciate that.
But you're right, Lois.
I'm gonna change.
I'm gonna do all the stuff for
you that Larry was doing.
No, Peter, I don't need any of that.
At our age, all I'm really
looking for in a husband
is someone who wants to watch
TV with me on a Saturday night
and isn't afraid to
pop a zit on my back.
"Afraid"? I love doing that.
It's like bubble wrap
you get to have sex with
every now and then.
I got a pretty good one
going right now, Peter.
You always do, Lois.
I love you.
Mm.
From that day forward, Peter
and Lois never again...
Ooh, nope, sorry, there's
still another scene left.
Well, Peter, turns out your
initial instinct was right.
You never should've let any
of your children contact you.
You said it.
From now on, I'm making sure my sperm
stays right where it belongs:
in the bathroom sink.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
We have fun down here.